Finding Aid for Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records
Clarke Historical Library
- Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records.
  - Job 728, Fairport Harbor, OH,1992 (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - Job 728, Fairport Harbor, OH, Bid, Receipts and Estimate,1992 (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Job 728, Fairport Harbor, OH, Contract,1992 (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI,1992 (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1992 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1992 (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI, Contract and Bid,1992 (Box 297, Folder 7)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1992 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1992 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI, Quality Control, Orders and Estimate,1992 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI, Receipts,1992 (Box 298, Folder 4)
  - Job 729, Milwaukee, WI, Specifications,1992 (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Job 730, Bay City,1992 (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Job 730, Bay City, Blue-line Drawings,1992 (Box 299, Folder 2)
  - Job 730, Bay City, Contract,1992 (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Job 730, Bay City, Correspondence,1992 (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - Job 730, Bay City, Transmittal,1992 (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Job 731, Saginaw River,1992 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Job 731, Saginaw River, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1992 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - Job 731, Saginaw River, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1992 (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - Job 731, Saginaw River, Contract,1992 (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - Job 731, Saginaw River, Correspondence and Bid,1992 (Box 300, Folder 4)
  - Job 731, Saginaw River, Receipts and Estimate,1992-1994 (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - Job 732, Green Bay, WI,1992-1993 (Box 300, Folder 6)
  - Job 732, Green Bay, WI, Bid, Estimate, Receipts,1992 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Job 732, Green Bay, WI, Blue-line Drawings,1992 (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - Job 732, Green Bay, WI, Contract and Specifications,1992-1993 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - Job 732, Green Bay, WI, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1992-1993 (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - Job 732, Green Bay, WI, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1992-1993 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - Job 732, Green Bay, WI, Photographs,1992 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - Job 733, Saginaw,1992 (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - Job 733, Saginaw, Bid, Receipts, Orders and Estimate,1992 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Job 733, Saginaw, Blue-line Drawings,1992 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - Job 733, Saginaw, Contract, 1 of 2,1992 (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Job 733, Saginaw, Contract, 2 of 2,1992 (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - Job 733, Saginaw, Photographs,1992 (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH,1992-1993 (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Bid and Receipts,1992-1993 (Box 302, Folder 7)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1992 (Box 302, Folder 8)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1992 (Box 302, Folder 9)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Claim,1993 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Contract,1992-1993 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Correspondence,1992-1993 (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Orders and Estimate,1992-1993 (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Photographs, 1 of 3,1993 (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Photographs, 2 of 3,1993 (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - Job 734, Cleveland, OH, Photographs, 3 of 3,1993 (Box 304, Folder 2)
  - Job 735, Milwaukee, WI,1992-1993 (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - Job 735, Milwaukee, WI, Bid and Estimate,1992 (Box 304, Folder 4)
  - Job 735, Milwaukee, WI, Contract and Specifications,1992-1993 (Box 304, Folder 5)
  - Job 735, Milwaukee, WI, Correspondence and Receipts,1992-1993 (Box 304, Folder 6)
  - Job 736, Frankfort,1993 (Box 304, Folder 7)
  - Job 737, Lake Erie, OH,1993 (Box 304, Folder 8)
  - Job 737, Lake Erie, OH, Bid,1993 (Box 304, Folder 9)
  - Job 738, Beulah,1993 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Job 739, Erie Harbor, PA,1993 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Job 739, Erie Harbor, PA, Bid and Specifications,1993 (Box 305, Folder 3)
  - Job 739, Erie Harbor, PA, Contract, Receipts, and Estimate,1993 (Box 305, Folder 4)
  - Job 740, Cleveland, OH,1993 (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - Job 741, Au Gres River,1993 (Box 305, Folder 6)
  - Job 741, Au Gres River, Bid and Specifications,1993 (Box 305, Folder 7)
  - Job 741, Au Gres River, Blue-line Drawings,1993 (Box 305, Folder 8)
  - Job 741, Au Gres River, Drawings,1993 (Box 305, Folder 9)
  - Job 741, Au Gres River, Contract, Receipts and Estimate,1993 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Job 742, Green Bay, WI,1993 (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - Job 742, Green Bay, WI, Bid and Specifications,1993 (Box 306, Folder 3)
  - Job 742, Green Bay, WI, Blue-line Drawings,1993 (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - Job 742, Green Bay, WI, Contract Correspondence,1993 (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - Job 742, Green Bay, WI, Receipts and Estimate,1993 (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo,1993 (Box 306, Folder 7)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Blue-line Drawings,1991-1993 (Box 306, Folder 8)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Claim,1994-1995 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Contract and Bid,1993 (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Correspondence, 1 of 3,1993-1995 (Box 307, Folder 3)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Correspondence, 2 of 3,1993-1995 (Box 307, Folder 4)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Correspondence, 3 of 3,1993-1995 (Box 307, Folder 5)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Orders and Estimate,1993-1994 (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Photographs, 1 of 2,1993 (Box 308, Folder 2)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Photographs, 2 of 2,1993 (Box 308, Folder 3)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Project Log Book,1994 (Box 308, Folder 4)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Quality Control,1994 (Box 308, Folder 5)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, Receipts,1993-1994 (Box 308, Folder 6)
  - Job 743, New Buffalo, StresCore Correspondence,1993-1994 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Job 744, West Harbor, OH,1993-1994 (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Job 744, West Harbor, OH, Bid,1993 (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Job 744, West Harbor, OH, Contract, Receipts and Estimate,1993 (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - Job 744, West Harbor, OH, Correspondence,1993 (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - Job 745, Dunkirk, NY,1993 (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - Job 745, Dunkirk, NY, All States Drilling and Blasting Correspondence,1993 (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Job 745, Dunkirk, NY, Bid and Estimate,1993 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - Job 745, Dunkirk, NY, Contract and Receipts,1993 (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - Job 745, Dunkirk, NY, Correspondence,1993 (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Job 745, Dunkirk, NY, Drawings,1993 (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Job 745, Dunkirk, NY, Photographs,1993 (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Job 745, Dunkirk, NY, Specifications,1993 (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Advance Case,1998 (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Advance Case,1999 (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, American Home Case,2001-2002 (Box 311, Folder 3)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Answer and Cross-Claim,1999 (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, City of Chicago Case Documents,2000-2001 (Box 311, Folder 5)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, City of Chicago vs ABH and Luedtke, 1 of 3,1998 (Box 311, Folder 6)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, City of Chicago vs ABH and Luedtke, 2 of 3,1998 (Box 311, Folder 7)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, City of Chicago vs ABH and Luedtke, 3 of 3,1998 (Box 311, Folder 8)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Claims, 1 of 3,1997 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Claims, 2 of 3,1997 (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Claims, 3 of 3,1997 (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Claims,1998 (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Contract, 1 of 3,1998 (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Contract, 2 of 3,1998 (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Contract, 3 of 3,1998 (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Contract Appendix, Part A, 1 of 2,1994 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Contract Appendix, Part A, 2 of 2,1994 (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Contract Appendix, Part B, 1 of 3,1994 (Box 313, Folder 3)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Contract Appendix, Part B, 2 of 3,1994 (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Contract Appendix, Part B, 3 of 3,1994 (Box 313, Folder 5)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Deposition, Sebeck, Jeffrey,2001 (Box 313, Folder 6)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, News Articles,1998, 2000, 2002 (Box 313, Folder 7)
  - Job 763, Chicago, IL, Settlement,2001-2002 (Box 313, Folder 8)
  - (Legal-size): Job 565, Milwaukee, WI, Bid Instructions,1982 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - (Legal-size): Job 567, Cleveland, Oh, Bid Instructions,1982 (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - (Legal-size): Job 569, Toledo, OH, Contract,1982 (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - (Legal-size): Job 578, Put-in-Bay, OH, Bid Instructions, Proposal and Contract,1982 (Box 314, Folder 4)
  - (Legal-size): Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Contract and Newspaper Clippings,1982-1985 (Box 314, Folder 5)
  - (Legal-size): Job 591, Harrisville, Abstract of Bids and Permit Application,1980, 1983-1984 (Box 314, Folder 6)
  - (Legal-size): Job 607, Calumet, IL, Incident Report,1984 (Box 314, Folder 7)
  - (Legal-size): Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Lease Agreement and Drawings,1985 (Box 314, Folder 8)
  - (Legal-size): Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Newspaper Clippings,1985 (Box 314, Folder 9)
  - (Legal-size): Job 615, Muskegon, Incident Reports,1985-1986 (Box 314, Folder 10)
  - (Legal-size): Job 629, Green Bay, WI, Incident Reports,1986 (Box 314, Folder 11)
  - (Legal-size): Job 632, Frankfort, Service Contract,1986 (Box 314, Folder 12)
  - (Legal-size): Job 634, Racine, WI, Incident Report,1986 (Box 314, Folder 13)
  - (Legal-size): Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Contract,1986 (Box 314, Folder 14)
  - (Legal-size): Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Estimate,1986 (Box 314, Folder 15)
  - (Legal-size): Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Incident Report,1987 (Box 314, Folder 16)
  - (Legal-size): Job 658, Kewaunee, WI, Incident Report,1987 (Box 314, Folder 17)
  - (Legal-size): Job 659, Saginaw, Land Lease,1987 (Box 314, Folder 18)
  - (Legal-size): Job 666, Evans, NY, Selvick Marine Correspondence,1988 (Box 314, Folder 19)
  - (Legal-size): Job 703, Cleveland, OH, Receipts,1990-1991 (Box 314, Folder 20)
  - (Legal-size): Job 704, Tonawanda, NY, Receipts,1991 (Box 314, Folder 21)
  - NLB Intake, Milwaukee, WI,1970 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Harbor of Refuge, Point Lookout,1970 (Box 315, Folder 2)
  - NLB Breakwater and Jetties, Ludington,1970 (Box 315, Folder 3)
  - NLB Breakwater and Jetties, Ludington, Bid,1970 (Box 315, Folder 4)
  - NLB Breakwater and Jetties, Ludington, Drawings, 1 of 2,1970 (Box 315, Folder 5)
  - NLB Breakwater and Jetties, Ludington, Drawings, 2 of 2,1970 (Box 315, Folder 6)
  - NLB Intake, Wilmette, IL,1970 (Box 315, Folder 7)
  - NLB 48-inch Water Intake, Manitowoc, WI,1971 (Box 315, Folder 8)
  - NLB Palisades Intake Structure Repairs, South Haven,1971 (Box 316, Folder 1)
  - NLB Water Intake, Cudahy, WI,1971 (Box 316, Folder 2)
  - NLB Baffle Wall Intake Structure, Point Beach, WI,1972 (Box 316, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Harbor of Refuge, New Buffalo,1973 (Box 316, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dike Disposal Area, Milwaukee, WI,1973 (Box 316, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater and Jetties, Oak Orchard, NY,1973 (Box 316, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, River Dredging, St. Mary’s River,1973 (Box 316, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dike Disposal Area, Huron Harbor, OH,1973 (Box 317, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dickinson Island,1974 (Box 317, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dickinson Island, Bid,1974 (Box 317, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Dickinson Island, Drawings,1974 (Box 317, Folder 4)
  - NLB Water Intake, Detroit,1974 (Box 317, Folder 5)
  - NLB Water Intake, Detroit, Drawings, 1 of 3,1974 (Box 317, Folder 6)
  - NLB Water Intake, Detroit, Drawings, 2 of 3,1974 (Box 317, Folder 7)
  - NLB Water Intake, Detroit, Drawings, 3 of 3,1974 (Box 317, Folder 8)
  - NLB Water Intake, Detroit, Contract,1974 (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - NLB Water Intake, Detroit,1974 (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Manitowoc, WI,1974 (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Buffalo Harbor, NY,1974 (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, River Widening, St. Mary’s River,1974 (Box 318, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, River Widening, St. Mary’s River, Drawings,1974 (Box 318, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Toledo, OH,1974 (Box 318, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, NLB 66-inch Water Intake, Bay County,1975 (Box 318, Folder 8)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Harbor of Refuge, Lexington,1975 (Box 318, Folder 9)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Harbor of Refuge, Lexington, Drawings,1975 (Box 318, Folder 10)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Saginaw Bay, Bid,1976 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Saginaw Bay, Estimates and Drawings,1976 (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Detroit, Bid,1976 (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Detroit, Drawings, 1 of 2,1976 (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Detroit, Drawings, 2 of 2,1976 (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Harbor of Refuge, Lexington, Drawings,1975 (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - NLB Intake, North Perry, OH,1976 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Cleveland, OH, Bid, 1 of 2,1976 (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Cleveland, OH, Bid, 2 of 2,1976 (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - NLB Consumers Power Company, West Olive, 1 of 2,1976 (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - NLB Consumers Power Company, West Olive, 2 of 2,1976 (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - NLB Consumers Power Company, West Olive, 1Blue-line Drawings,1976 (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Bolles Harbor,1977 (Box 320, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Bolles Harbor, Blue-line Drawings,1977 (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Erie, PA,1978 (Box 321, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Huron Harbor, OH,1978 (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Green Bay, WI,1978 (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Port Washington, WI,1979 (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Manitowoc Harbor, WI,1981 (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - NLB City of Kenosha Water Utility, Kenosha, WI,1981 (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - NLB Burgess and Niple, Lake County, OH,1981 (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - NLB Rock Barrier, Port Austin,1989 (Box 322, Folder 4)
  - NLB Dockwall, Racine, WI,1989 (Box 322, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Duluth, MN,1989 (Box 322, Folder 6)
  - NLB Dredging, Toledo, OH,1989 (Box 322, Folder 7)
  - NLB Kirkland Crib Rehabilitation, Bid, Cleveland, OH, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 323, Folder 1)
  - NLB Kirkland Crib Rehabilitation, Bid, Cleveland, OH, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 323, Folder 2)
  - NLB Bulkhead Rehabilitation, Rocky River, OH,1990 (Box 323, Folder 3)
  - NLB Pier Restoration, Bid, Grosse Ile, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 323, Folder 4)
  - NLB Pier Restoration, Bid, Grosse Ile, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 323, Folder 5)
  - NLB Breakwater Extension, Sandusky, OH,1990 (Box 323, Folder 6)
  - NLB Clean Intake Forbay, Dunkirk Station, NY,1990 (Box 323, Folder 7)
  - NLB Channel Construction, Piling, Village of Manistee, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 324, Folder 1)
  - NLB Channel Construction, Piling, Village of Manistee, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 324, Folder 2)
  - NLB Channel Construction, Piling, Blue-lines, Village of Manistee,1990 (Box 324, Folder 3)
  - NLB Shoreline Construction, Bid, Manistee, MI, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 324, Folder 4)
  - NLB Shoreline Construction, Bid, Manistee, MI, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 324, Folder 5)
  - NLB Mooring for Steamer W.M.G. Mather, Cleveland, OH,1990 (Box 325, Folder 1)
  - NLB Intake, Zion, IL,1990 (Box 325, Folder 2)
  - NLB Underwater Bridge, Muskegon County,1990 (Box 325, Folder 3)
  - NLB Dredge Boat Slip, Saginaw Bay,1990 (Box 325, Folder 4)
  - NLB Marina Development, Manistee,1990 (Box 325, Folder 5)
  - NLB Breakwaters, Waukegan, IL,1990 (Box 325, Folder 6)
  - NLB USCOE/ Detroit, Clinton River,1990 (Box 325, Folder 7)
  - NLB Transmission Main, Grand Rapids,1990 (Box 325, Folder 8)
  - NLB Intake Structure, Bid, Instructions, Bridgman, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 325, Folder 9)
  - NLB Intake Structure, Bid, Instructions, Bridgman, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 325, Folder 10)
  - NLB Marina Extension, Suttons Bay,1991 (Box 326, Folder 1)
  - NLB Small Boat Harbor, Buffalo, NY,1991 (Box 326, Folder 2)
  - NLB Channel Cable Crossing, Grosse Isle,1991 (Box 326, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater Repairs, Two Harbors, MN,1991 (Box 326, Folder 4)
  - NLB Terminal Dock Replacement, Bay City,1991 (Box 326, Folder 5)
  - NLB Terminal Dock Replacement, Bay City, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 326, Folder 6)
  - NLB Terminal Dock Replacement, Bay City, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 326, Folder 7)
  - NLB Iroquois Gas Transmission System, St. Lawrence River, NY,1991 (Box 326, Folder 8)
  - NLB Replacement of Three Fender Walls at Carfloat, Detroit,1991 (Box 326, Folder 9)
  - NLB Replacement of Three Fender Walls at Carfloat, Detroit, Photographs,1991 (Box 326, Folder 10)
  - NLB Intake Chlorination Pipeline, St. Joseph,1991 (Box 327, Folder 1)
  - NLB Intake Chlorination Pipeline, St. Joseph, Photographs,1991 (Box 327, Folder 2)
  - NLB Rehabilitation of Lorain West Breakwater Lighthouse, Lorain, OH,1991 (Box 327, Folder 3)
  - NLB Whitestone Point Intake Crib, Bay City,1991 (Box 327, Folder 4)
  - NLB 3-inch Zebra Mussel Lines, Buffalo, NY,1991 (Box 327, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, West Retreatment Repair, Ontonagon, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 327, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, West Retreatment Repair, Ontonagon, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 327, Folder 7)
  - NLB Rip Rap Breakwater, St. Ignace,1991 (Box 328, Folder 1)
  - NLB Super Chlorination of Water Plant Intakes, Wilmette, IL,1991 (Box 328, Folder 2)
  - NLB Zebra Mussel Control, Wyoming,1991 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - NLB Dock Slip Extension, Cleveland – Cuyahoga, OH,1991 (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - NLB Raw Water Intake Phase 2, Monroe,1992 (Box 328, Folder 5)
  - NLB Lake Intake Facilities, Saginaw – Midland,1992 (Box 328, Folder 6)
  - NLB Lake Intake Facilities, Saginaw – Midland, Blue-lines and Drawings,1992 (Box 328, Folder 7)
  - NLB Water System Improvements, North Brook, IL,1992 (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - NLB New Fishing Pier, Harbor Beach,1992 (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - NLB New Fishing Pier, Harbor Beach, Blue-lines and Photographs,1992 (Box 329, Folder 3)
  - NLB Water Filtration Plant, New Buffalo,1992 (Box 329, Folder 4)
  - NLB Breakwater Dock Construction, North Manitou Island,1992 (Box 329, Folder 5)
  - NLB City Marina, Munising,1992 (Box 330, Folder 1)
  - NLB City Marina, Munising, Blue-lines and Photographs,1992 (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - NLB Water Filtration Plant, Muskegon,1992 (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. CG, Repair Boat Slip, Lorain, OH,1992 (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - NLB Bay Entrance Channel, Bay City,1992 (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - NLB Bay Entrance Channel, Bay City, Blue-lines, 1 of 2,1992 (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - NLB Bay Entrance Channel, Bay City, Blue-lines, 2 of 2,1992 (Box 330, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater Repairs, Harbor Beach, 1 of 2,1992 (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater Repairs, Harbor Beach, 2 of 2,1992 (Box 331, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Breakwater Repairs, Harbor Beach, Blue-lines,1992 (Box 331, Folder 3)
  - NLB Pile Cluster Repair, St. Joseph,1992 (Box 331, Folder 4)
  - NLB Remedial Action, Frankfort,1992 (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - NLB Water Treatment Plant Improvements, Muskegon Heights,1992 (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - NLB New Cat Walks and Sheet Pile Firewalls, Sandusky, OH,1992 (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Fishing Pier, Charlevoix, 1 of 2,1992 (Box 331, Folder 8)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Fishing Pier, Charlevoix, 2 of 2,1992 (Box 331, Folder 9)
  - NLB Terminal Dock Replacement, Traverse City,1992 (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - NLB Terminal Dock Replacement, Traverse City, Blue-lines,1992 (Box 332, Folder 2)
  - NLB Shoreline Protection and Barge Removal, Perry, OH,1992 (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Confined Disposal Facility, Toledo, OH,1992 (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - NLB Zebra Mussel Control, Grand Rapids,1992 (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - NLB Dockwall Extension, Burns Harbor, IN,1992 (Box 332, Folder 6)
  - NLB Fuel Storage Tanks, South Manitou Island,1992 (Box 332, Folder 7)
  - NLB Raw Water Pump Station, Lexington,1992 (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - NLB Raw Water Pump Station, Lexington, Blue-lines,1992 (Box 332, Folder 9)
  - NLB ESELCO Sault St. Marie, 1 of 2,1993 (Box 333, Folder 1)
  - NLB ESELCO Sault St. Marie, 2 of 2,1993 (Box 333, Folder 2)
  - NLB ESELCO Sault St. Marie, Blue-lines,1993 (Box 333, Folder 3)
  - NLB Consumers Power Company, Wellston,1993 (Box 333, Folder 4)
  - NLB Consumers Power Company, Wellston, Drawings,1993 (Box 333, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Ontonagon,1993 (Box 333, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Ontonagon, Blue-lines, 1 of 2,1993 (Box 334, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Ontonagon, Blue-lines, 2 of 2,1993 (Box 334, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Ontonagon, Blue-lines, Photographs,1993 (Box 334, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Lee County, OH,1993 (Box 334, Folder 4)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Clark County, MO,1993 (Box 334, Folder 5)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Lewis and Marion Counties, MO,1993 (Box 334, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Marion County, MO,1993 (Box 334, Folder 7)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Adams and Pike Counties, IL,1993 (Box 334, Folder 8)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Levee Repair, Gregory Drainage District, MO,1993 (Box 334, Folder 9)
  - NLB Townsend and Bottum Barrier Nets, Ludington,1993 (Box 334, Folder 10)
  - NLB Mazurik Access Area, Ottawa County, OH,1993 (Box 334, Folder 11)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Pier and Breakwater Repairs, Manistee Harbor, Proposal, 1 of 2,1994 (Box 334, Folder 12)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Pier and Breakwater Repairs, Manistee Harbor, Proposal, 2 of 2,1994 (Box 335, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Pier and Breakwater Repairs, Manistee Harbor, Blue-lines, 1 of 2,1994 (Box 335, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Revetment Pier and Breakwater Repairs, Manistee Harbor, Blue-lines, 2 of 2,1994 (Box 335, Folder 3)
  - NLB City Park Improvements, Au Gres,1994 (Box 335, Folder 4)
  - NLB Indiana Port Commissions, Jeffersonville, IN,1994 (Box 335, Folder 5)
  - NLB Whiskey Island Partners, Cleveland, OH,1994 (Box 335, Folder 6)
  - NLB Department of Transportation, Mevidian Technologies, Inc. Manistee Lake, Big Rapids,1994 (Box 335, Folder 7)
  - NLB Meridian Technologies, Inc., Manistee Lake,1994 (Box 335, Folder 8)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Reads Landing, MN,1994 (Box 335, Folder 9)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Crane H.J. Schwart, Lake Superior, 1 of 2,1994 (Box 336, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Crane H.J. Schwart, Lake Superior, 2 of 2,1994 (Box 336, Folder 2)
  - NLB Edison Sault Electric Company, Sault St. Marie,1994 (Box 336, Folder 3)
  - NLB Edison Sault Electric Company, Sault St. Marie, Blue-lines and Drawings,1994 (Box 336, Folder 4)
  - NLB Consumers Power Company, Ludington,1994 (Box 336, Folder 5)
  - NLB Consumers Power Company, Ludington,1995 (Box 337, Folder 1)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Manistee Harbor,1995 (Box 337, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Manistee Harbor, Blue-line Drawings, 1 of 2,1995 (Box 337, Folder 3)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Manistee Harbor, Blue-line Drawings, 2 of 2,1995 (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - NLB Consumers Power Company, Newaygo County,1995 (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - NLB Thatcher Engineering Corporation, Gary, IN,1995 (Box 337, Folder 6)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, East Pier Repair, Cleveland, OH,1995 (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - NLB 108-inch Water Intake Line, Milwaukee, WI,1995 (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - NLB U.S. Engineers, Black Rock Lock, Erie County, NY,1995 (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - NLB Hodenpyl Tailrace Wall Rehabilitation, Mesick,1995 (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - NLB Mohawk Power Co. Niagara, NY,1995-1996 (Box 338, Folder 5)